lolzparade.com 2013-05-27

# 

We take your privacy very seriously. 

##  Introduction 

DailyPix, Inc. (“DailyPix”) takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously. 

This privacy policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully. 

##  Website Visitors 

Like most website operators, DailyPix collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. DailyPix’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how DailyPix’s visitors use its website. From time to time, DailyPix may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

DailyPix also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. DailyPix does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

##  Aggregated Statistics 

DailyPix may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, DailyPix may monitor the most popular collections on DailyPix.com. DailyPix may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, DailyPix does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

##  Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information 

DailyPix discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on DailyPix’s behalf or to provide services available at DailyPix’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using DailyPix’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if DailyPix or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that DailyPix goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of DailyPix may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, DailyPix will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. 

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, DailyPix discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when DailyPix believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of DailyPix, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a DailyPix website and have supplied your email address, DailyPix may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with DailyPix and its products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. DailyPix takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

##  Cookies 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. DailyPix uses cookies to help DailyPix identify and track visitors, their usage of DailyPix websites, and their website access preferences. DailyPix visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using DailyPix’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of DailyPix’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

##  Ads 

Ads appearing on any DailyPix websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by DailyPix and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

##  Links to Third Party Sites 

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by DailyPix. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DailyPix does not own or control, or employees that DailyPix does not manage. A DailyPix website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and DailyPix and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party. 

##  Privacy Policy Changes 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, DailyPix may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in DailyPix’s sole discretion. DailyPix encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

##  Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please contact us.
